Guide to the Gay Men's Health Crisis records
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series XII. Public Policy Department, 1983-1997, n.d.; 38.75 boxes
  - XII. A. Administrative Files, 1983-1993, n.d.; 19 boxes
    - Legislation
      - Prohibits HIV infected health care workers from performing invasive procedures (A. 4835), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 30)
      - Prompt contracting (Governor's Program Bill #101), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 31)
      - Rape testing (A. 6895), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 32)
      - Rape Victims Service Act of 1991 (S. 2192) (Box 360, Folder 33)
      - Reports by AIDS-related agencies (A. 1882), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 34)
      - Right to Privacy constitutional amendment (A. 6654), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 35)
      - Safekeeping of health care proxies (A. 6629), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 36)
      - Sale of blood by HIV-infected persons (A. 4878/S. 3753), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 37)
      - Self-designated blood donations (S. 601), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 38)
      - Small business health insurance (S. 2426/A. 3719), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 39)
      - Statute of limitations for human rights cases (A. 1959/S. 1158), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 40)
      - Succession to apartment lease (S. 6459), 1987 (Box 360, Folder 41)
      - Survey of inmates for HIV infection (A. 5218), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 42)
      - Survey of state prisons for HIV prevalence (A. 4792), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 43)
      - Testing Confidentiality Act (A. 6924-C), 1987-1988 (Box 360, Folder 44)
      - Testing, mandatory reporting, and contact tracing (A. 1565), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 45)
      - Testing of inmates (A. 5571), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 46)
      - Testing without parental consent (A. 7049), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 47)
      - Uniformed officers exposure to AIDS (S. 729), 1991 (Box 360, Folder 48)
      - Wiecker Bill (H.R. 5233), 1986 (Box 361, Folder 1)
      - Workers' Compensation/HIV infection (S. 8280), 1990 (Box 361, Folder 2)
    - Lesbian AIDS Project, 1992 (Box 361, Folder 3)
    - Long term care, 1988-1990 (Box 361, Folder 4)
    - Lundine briefing, 1986 (Box 361, Folder 5)
    - Maloney visit, 1986 (Box 361, Folder 6)
    - Mandatory testing, 1989 (Box 361, Folder 7)
    - Mayoral forum, 1989 (Box 361, Folder 8)
    - Medicaid MUTS lawsuit, 1989 (Box 361, Folder 9-10)
    - Medicaid reimbursement, 1989 (Box 361, Folder 11)
    - Medicare, 1989 (Box 361, Folder 12)
    - Memoranda, 1990-1992, 1995-1996 (Box 361, Folder 13)
    - Monthly reports, 1988-1995 (Box 361, Folder 14-15)
    - National Organizations Responding to AIDS, 1989 (Box 361, Folder 16)
    - New Jersey reportability, 1986 (Box 361, Folder 17)
    - New York AIDS Coalition
      - General
        - 1991
          - Mar-Apr (Box 361, Folder 18)
          - May-Oct (Box 362, Folder 1)
      - Advisory Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 362, Folder 2)
      - AIDS Awareness Day, 1991-1992 (Box 362, Folder 3-4)
      - Albany Conference, 1989 (Box 362, Folder 5)
      - Beat the Clock, 1988 (Box 362, Folder 6)
      - City Committee for AIDS Funding Merger, 1989 (Box 362, Folder 7)
      - Debriefing memoranda, 1989 (Box 362, Folder 8)
      - Fall 1991 Conference, 1990-1991 (Box 362, Folder 9)
      - Finances, 1988-1989 (Box 362, Folder 10)
      - Funding agenda, 1989 (Box 362, Folder 11)
      - Legislative issues, 1988 (Box 362, Folder 12)
      - Mailings, 1988-1989 (Box 362, Folder 13)
      - Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 363, Folder 1)
      - New York City budget process, 1993 (Box 363, Folder 2)
      - Press conference, 1988 (Box 363, Folder 3)
      - Press packet, 1988-1989 (Box 363, Folder 4)
      - Press releases, 1989 (Box 363, Folder 5)
      - Statement of purpose, 1988 (Box 363, Folder 6)
    - New York AIDS Consortium, 1986-1989 (Box 363, Folder 7-9)
    - New York City budget
      - General
        - 1985-1986 (Box 363, Folder 10)
        - 1987, 1991-1993 (Box 364, Folder 1-2)
      - Funding for AIDS programs, 1990-1991 (Box 364, Folder 3)
    - New York City Council Subcommittee on Women, 1992-1993 (Box 364, Folder 4)
    - New York City Department of Health, 1992 (Box 364, Folder 5)
    - New York City job applications, 1988 (Box 364, Folder 6)
    - New York State Assembly Puerto Rican/Hispanic Task Force, 1989-1990 (Box 364, Folder 7)
    - New York State budget
      - General, 1987-1993 (Box 364, Folder 8-10)
      - Funding for AIDS programs, 1987-1992 (Box 364, Folder 11-14)
    - New York State Department of Health
      - General, 1987-1988 (Box 365, Folder 1)
      - Five year plan, 1989-1991 (Box 365, Folder 2-3)
      - Legislation, 1988-1993 (Box 365, Folder 4-6)
      - Legislature Health Insurance Subcommittees, 1988-1989 (Box 365, Folder 7)
    - People of Color and AIDS, 1985-1988 (Box 365, Folder 8-11)
    - Press releases, 1992, 1995-1997 (Box 365, Folder 12)
    - Prison issues
      - General, 1991-1992 (Box 365, Folder 13)
      - Alliance for Inmates with AIDS, 1990-1992 (Box 366, Folder 1)
    - Prisoners, 1986-1989 (Box 366, Folder 2)
    - Rent stabilization code, 1987 (Box 366, Folder 3)
    - Ryan White CARE Act, 1990-1991 (Box 366, Folder 4-5)
    - Seroprevalance, 1988 (Box 366, Folder 6)
    - Social Security Income Level III
      - AIDS Housing Bill, 1989-1990 (Box 366, Folder 7)
      - Background, 1990 (Box 366, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 366, Folder 9)
      - HIV/AIDS community-based organizations
        - 1990
          - Jan-Mar (Box 366, Folder 10)
          - Apr-Nov (Box 367, Folder 1)
      - Long term care, 1990 (Box 367, Folder 2)
      - Press releases, 1990-1991 (Box 367, Folder 3)
      - Standards of care, 1989-1990 (Box 367, Folder 4-5)
    - State of New York Mortgage Authority (SONYMA), 1991 (Box 367, Folder 6)
    - Substance abuse, 1988-1992 (Box 367, Folder 7-8)
    - Substance Abuse Workgroup
      - HIV care, 1991-1992 (Box 367, Folder 9)
      - Medical and Health Research Association, 1991 (Box 367, Folder 10)
      - Report, 1993 (Box 367, Folder 11)
    - Sweeney, Timothy J., chronological file, 1988-1992 (Box 367, Folder 12-13)
    - Task Force on Women and AIDS, 1992 (Box 367, Folder 14)
    - TB Working Group
      - Budget analysis, 1993 (Box 368, Folder 1)
      - Community Forum, 1992-1993 (Box 368, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 368, Folder 3)
      - GMHC's response to AIDS, 1993 (Box 368, Folder 4)
      - Letter to the New York City Board of Health, 1992-1993 (Box 368, Folder 5)
      - Letter to Norman Steisel on Department of Health hires, 1992 (Box 368, Folder 6)
      - Meetings with New York City Department of Health, 1992 (Box 368, Folder 7)
      - Memoranda, 1992-1993 (Box 368, Folder 8-10)
      - Miscellaneous, 1992-1993 (Box 368, Folder 11)
      - New York AIDS Coalition on TB, 1993 (Box 368, Folder 12)
      - New York City Department of Health, 1992-1993 (Box 368, Folder 13)
      - New York State Department of Health, 1992-1993 (Box 368, Folder 14)
      - News, 1992-1993 (Box 368, Folder 15)
      - Papers, 1992-1993 (Box 368, Folder 16)
      - Response to City Blueprint, 1992 (Box 369, Folder 1)
      - TB and HIV, 1992-1993 (Box 369, Folder 2)
    - Testimony, 1986-1989 (Box 369, Folder 3-4)
    - Universal health care, 1987-1989 (Box 369, Folder 5)
    - Verhoef, Hans Paul, 1988-1989 (Box 369, Folder 6)
    - Women and AIDS
      - Articles, 1986-1987 (Box 369, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 369, Folder 8)
      - New York State hearings, 1987 (Box 369, Folder 9)
    - Women and AIDS Conference, 1991 (Box 369, Folder 10)
    - Women and AIDS Policy Working Group
      - General, 1991-1992 (Box 369, Folder 11-12)
      - Mandatory Testing of Health Care Workers, 1991 (Box 370, Folder 1)
      - Mandatory Testing of Pregnant Women and Newborns, 1991 (Box 370, Folder 2)
      - Women in Prison, 1990-1991 (Box 370, Folder 3)
      - Women, Substance Abuse, and HIV, 1992 (Box 370, Folder 4)
    - Women and AIDS Project, 1987-1989 (Box 370, Folder 5)
    - Women + HIV
      - General, 1989-1992, n.d. (Box 370, Folder 6-7)
      - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 370, Folder 8)
      - National Institutes of Health hearing on women's health research, 1990-1992 (Box 370, Folder 9)
    - Women's Action Committee, 1991 (Box 370, Folder 10)
    - Women's Treatment Issues, 1991-1992 (Box 370, Folder 11)
    - World AIDS Day, 1989 (Box 370, Folder 12)
  - XII. B. Alcohol and Other Drugs Workgroup, 1987-1997; 2 boxes
    The Alcohol and Other Drugs Workgroup was part of the New York City HIV Health and Human Services Planning Council. Richard Elovich was the chairperson of the Workgroup and the director of GMHC's Substance Use Counseling and Education program. The group worked on developing programs for HIV-infected substance abusers and expanding Ryan White CARE Act funding for these types of programs.
    This subseries contains correspondence, memoranda, minutes, and reports from the Alcohol and Other Drugs Workgroup. Included here is correspondence with state and federal officials regarding expansion of funding and development of program drug users with HIV/AIDS.
    - Alcohol and Other Drugs group materials
      - Curriculum and screening tools, 1995 (Box 370, Folder 13)
      - National San Francisco Substance Abuse Needs Assessment, 1991 (Box 371, Folder 1)
      - Public Policy
        - Continuum of service needs for the HIV-infected active drug-user, 1992 (Box 371, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 371, Folder 3-4)
        - Funding pool issue, 1995 (Box 371, Folder 5)
        - Grant and award, 1996 (Box 371, Folder 6)
        - Health Systems Agency, 1993, 1996 (Box 371, Folder 7-8)
        - HIV Planning Council minutes, 1994 (Box 371, Folder 9)
        - Medical and Health Research Association report, 1995 (Box 371, Folder 10)
        - Meeting, 1995 (Box 371, Folder 11)
        - Membership, 1994-1995 (Box 371, Folder 12)
        - Needle exchange, 1992-1993 (Box 371, Folder 13)
        - Office of Alcoholism and Substance Abuse, 1992-1993 (Box 371, Folder 14)
        - Planning and Evaluation Committee
          - Case management, 1996 (Box 372, Folder 1)
          - Minutes, 1994-1996 (Box 372, Folder 2-3)
          - Report and planning principles, 1995-1996 (Box 372, Folder 4)
          - Strategic planning retreat, 1995 (Box 372, Folder 5)
          - Syringes, 1995? (Box 372, Folder 6)
        - Planning principles, 1995 (Box 372, Folder 7)
        - PWA report, 1992-1993 (Box 372, Folder 8)
        - Recovery readiness, 1993 (Box 372, Folder 9)
        - Requests for proposals, 1991-1996 (Box 372, Folder 10-12)
        - Ryan White CARE Act reauthorization, 1995 (Box 372, Folder 13)
        - Substance abuse treatment services and providers, 1992-1993 (Box 373, Folder 1)
        - Substance abuse workgroup notes, 1992 (Box 373, Folder 2)
        - United States Health Resources and Services Administration policy, 1996 (Box 373, Folder 3)
      - Research materials, 1987-1991 (Box 373, Folder 4)
    - Elovich, Richard, 1995 (Box 373, Folder 5)
    - Harm reduction, 1994-1995 (Box 406, Folder 12)
    - HIV Planning Council
      - General, 1996-1997 (Box 373, Folder 6-7)
      - Consolidated planning tool, 1996 (Box 373, Folder 8)
      - Ryan White CARE Act funding, 1996 (Box 373, Folder 9)
    - Hunter College Center on AIDS, Drugs, and Community Health, 1993-1996 (Box 373, Folder 10)
    - Needle exchange
      - AmFar, 1990-1992 (Box 373, Folder 11)
      - Beth Israel, 1994 (Box 373, Folder 12)
      - Funding, 1992-1993 (Box 373, Folder 13)
      - GMHC Injecting Drug Users information for staff, 1991-1994 (Box 373, Folder 14)
      - Grants, 1993 (Box 373, Folder 15)
      - Kennedy, Rory, 1995 (Box 373, Folder 16)
      - New York State, 1992-1993 (Box 373, Folder 17)
    - Ryan White CARE Act and Alcohol and Other Drugs Workgroup
      - Adolescents, 1993 (Box 373, Folder 18)
      - AIDS Institute funded programs, 1993-1994 (Box 373, Folder 19)
      - Year 6 priorities
        - 1995 (Box 373, Folder 20)
        - 1996 (Box 374, Folder 1)
  - XII. C. Committee for AIDS Funding, 1987-1991; 2.25 boxes
    The Committee for AIDS Funding was a coalition of members of various AIDS organizations in New York City which lobbied the New York City government for increased funding of AIDS programs and fair HIV/AIDS policies. Timothy J. Sweeney was the chairperson.
    Included here are agenda and minutes from Committee meetings, correspondence with various members of the Committee and city officials, and material on the Citywide Speak Out on AIDS! at which Committee members gave testimony on underfunded programs, unfair policies towards PWAs, and other issues.
    - Agenda and minutes, 1987-1990 (Box 374, Folder 2-4)
    - A Call to Action, 1988 (Box 374, Folder 5)
    - Citywide Speakout on AIDS!, 1988-1989 (Box 374, Folder 6-8)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 374, Folder 9-12)
    - Funding agenda, 1988-1990 (Box 375, Folder 1-3)
    - Memoranda, 1987-1991 (Box 375, Folder 4-6)
    - Minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 375, Folder 7)
    - New York City budget, 1987-1990 (Box 375, Folder 8-10)
    - New York State budget, 1989 (Box 375, Folder 11)
    - Press releases and clippings, 1987-1990 (Box 376, Folder 1-4)
  - XII. D. Organizations File, 1983-1993; 14 boxes
    This subseries contains documentation relating to AIDS organizations and other agencies related to GMHC's mission. Included here are correspondence and reports of the AIDS Action Council and the New York AIDS Coalition, files on The Names Project which produced the AIDS quilts, and the Presidential Commission on the HIV Epidemic.
    - VI-VIII International Conferences on AIDS, 1989-1991 (Box 376, Folder 5-7)
    - ACT-UP, 1987-1989 (Box 376, Folder 8)
    - AIDS Action Council
      - Absentee balloting, 1990-1992 (Box 376, Folder 9)
      - Arrowwood update, 1991 (Box 376, Folder 10)
      - Board of Directors
        - General
          - 1990-1991 May (Box 376, Folder 11-13)
          - 1991 Jul-Dec (Box 377, Folder 1)
        - Meeting, 1991 (Box 377, Folder 2)
        - Retreat, 1991 (Box 377, Folder 3)
      - Congressional profiles, 1990? (Box 377, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 377, Folder 5)
      - Finances, 1990 (Box 377, Folder 6)
      - Flyers, 1992 (Box 377, Folder 7)
      - Health care, 1991-1992 (Box 377, Folder 8)
      - HIV testing in New York State, 1991-1992 (Box 377, Folder 9)
      - Labor, 1992 (Box 377, Folder 10)
      - Legislative action, 1990 (Box 377, Folder 11)
      - Levi, Jeff, 1989-1990 (Box 377, Folder 12-13)
      - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1990? (Box 377, Folder 14)
      - National Organizations Responding to AIDS, 1988-1991
        - 1988-1990 (Box 377, Folder 15)
        - 1991 (Box 378, Folder 1)
      - Outreach during Democratic National Convention week, 1992 (Box 378, Folder 2)
      - Press releases, 1991 (Box 378, Folder 3)
      - Public affairs manual, 1990? (Box 378, Folder 4)
      - Public Policy Committee
        - General, 1990-1993 (Box 378, Folder 5-6)
        - Meetings
          - 1990-1991 Mar (Box 378, Folder 7-9)
          - 1991 May (Box 379, Folder 1)
      - Ryan White CARE Act, 1991-1993 (Box 379, Folder 2)
      - Spanish translations, 1990? (Box 379, Folder 3)
      - Tax day, 1992? (Box 379, Folder 4)
    - AIDS Action Emergency Response Network, 1990? (Box 379, Folder 5)
    - AIDS Advisory Council
      - Correspondence 1986-1990 (Box 379, Folder 6)
      - Meetings, 1987-1990 (Box 379, Folder 7-10)
    - AIDS Alliance of New York City, 1991 (Box 379, Folder 11)
    - AIDS Center of Queens County, 1990? (Box 379, Folder 12)
    - AIDS Community Services, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 13)
    - AIDS Drug Assistance Program, 1991 (Box 379, Folder 14)
    - AIDS National Interfaith Network, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 15)
    - AIDS Project Los Angeles, 1987 (Box 379, Folder 16)
    - AIDS Resource Center, 1986-1990, 1993 (Box 380, Folder 1)
    - AIDS Treatment Activist Conference, 1990 (Box 380, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Treatment Registry, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 3)
    - American Civil Liberties Union
      - AIDS policy update, 1990 (Box 380, Folder 4-5)
      - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 380, Folder 6)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research (AMFAR), 1987-1990 (Box 380, Folder 7)
    - American Hospital Association, 1987 (Box 380, Folder 8)
    - American Public Health Association, 1986-1988 (Box 380, Folder 9)
    - American Social Health Association, 1983-1986 (Box 380, Folder 10)
    - Association for Drug Abuse and Treatment Inc. (ADAPT), 1987? (Box 380, Folder 11)
    - Association of Lesbian and Gay Executive Directors, 1990 (Box 380, Folder 12)
    - Black Leadership Commission on AIDS, 1988-1990 (Box 380, Folder 13)
    - Blue Cross and Blue Shield, 1989-1991 (Box 380, Folder 14)
    - Boston AIDS Consortium, 1988 (Box 381, Folder 1)
    - Breakfast Group, 1986 (Box 381, Folder 2)
    - California Medical Association, 1987-1988 (Box 381, Folder 3)
    - Catholic Health Association, 1987-1988 (Box 381, Folder 4)
    - Center for Constitutional Rights and Center for Women Policy Studies, 1988-1989 (Box 381, Folder 5)
    - Central Conference of American Rabbis, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 6)
    - Citizens Commission on AIDS for New York City and Northern New Jersey
      - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 381, Folder 7)
      - Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 381, Folder 8-9)
    - Citizens' Committee for Children of New York, 1988 (Box 381, Folder 10)
    - The City Project, 1988 (Box 381, Folder 11)
    - Coalition for the Homeless, 1988-1990 (Box 381, Folder 12)
    - The Coalition of Voluntary Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Alcoholism Agencies, Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 381, Folder 13)
    - Coalition on Economic Priorities, 1988-1989 (Box 381, Folder 14)
    - Columbia University Project, 1990-1991 (Box 381, Folder 15)
    - Community Research Initiative, 1986-1987 (Box 382, Folder 1)
    - Council of Medical School Deans, 1988 (Box 382, Folder 2)
    - The Council of State Governments, 1986, 1991 (Box 382, Folder 3)
    - Design Industries Foundation for AIDS (DIFFA), 1985-1988 (Box 382, Folder 4)
    - The Empire State Pride Agenda, 1991 (Box 382, Folder 5)
    - Fiscal Policy Institute, 1991 (Box 382, Folder 6)
    - Food and Drug Administration (FDA)
      - Blood products, 1988-1990 (Box 382, Folder 7)
      - Meeting with GMHC, 1988 (Box 382, Folder 8)
      - New drugs, 1987-1991 (Box 382, Folder 9)
    - The Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD), 1986-1987 (Box 382, Folder 10)
    - Gay Men of African Descent, 1987 (Box 382, Folder 11)
    - Greater New York Hospital Association, 1987-1989 (Box 382, Folder 12-14)
    - Harvard AIDS Institute, 1989 (Box 382, Folder 15)
    - Health Care Financing Administration Medicare Regulations, 1989-1990 (Box 382, Folder 16)
    - Health Systems Agency of New York City
      - Coordinating Committee Recommendations, 1990 (Box 382, Folder 17)
      - Date Resource Workgroup, 1990 (Box 383, Folder 1)
      - Five Year Plan Review, 1990 (Box 383, Folder 2)
      - Legislative Workgroup, 1991 (Box 383, Folder 3)
      - Long-term Care Plan, 1989 (Box 383, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous, 1988-1991 (Box 383, Folder 5)
      - Project Review Manual, 1989 (Box 383, Folder 6)
    - Hispanic AIDS Forum, 1990 (Box 383, Folder 7)
    - Hispanic Commission on AIDS, 1989 (Box 383, Folder 8)
    - Housing Works, 1990 (Box 383, Folder 9)
    - Human Rights Campaign Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 383, Folder 10)
    - Human Services Council of New York City, 1990-1992 (Box 383, Folder 11)
    - Hyacinth Foundation AIDS Project, 1990 (Box 383, Folder 12)
    - Institute for the Protection of Lesbian and Gay Youth, 1986-1987 (Box 383, Folder 13)
    - Interfaith AIDS Ministries, 1990-1991 (Box 383, Folder 14)
    - Lambda Independent Democrats, 1988 (Box 383, Folder 15)
    - Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1988-1989 (Box 383, Folder 16)
    - Leadership Institute, 1985-1987 (Box 383, Folder 17)
    - Legal Action Center, 1989-1990 (Box 384, Folder 1)
    - Living with AIDS Fund, 1988 (Box 384, Folder 2)
    - Long Island Association for AIDS Care, 1990 (Box 384, Folder 3)
    - March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1986-1987, 1991-1993 (Box 384, Folder 4)
    - Mayor's Office of the Lesbian and Gay Community, 1990 (Box 384, Folder 5)
    - MetPath, 1986 (Box 384, Folder 6)
    - Minority Task Force on AIDS, 1987-1988, 1991-1992 (Box 384, Folder 7-8)
    - Multitasking Systems, 1988? (Box 384, Folder 9)
    - The Names Project
      - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 384, Folder 10)
      - Finances, 1988 (Box 384, Folder 11)
      - Host Committee, 1988 (Box 384, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous, 1987-1988 (Box 384, Folder 13)
      - Opening Ceremony, 1988 (Box 384, Folder 14)
      - Press releases, 1988 (Box 384, Folder 15)
      - Quilt in New York, 1988 (Box 384, Folder 16)
    - National AIDS Lobby Days, 1991 (Box 384, Folder 17)
    - National AIDS Network
      - General, 1986-1989 (Box 384, Folder 18)
      - AIDS into the 90s, 1987 (Box 384, Folder 19)
      - Skills Building Conference, 1988 (Box 384, Folder 20)
    - National AIDS Organizations, 1991 (Box 385, Folder 1)
    - National Association of People with AIDS, 1990 (Box 385, Folder 2)
    - National Commission on AIDS, 1989, 1992 (Box 385, Folder 3)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force
      - Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 385, Folder 4)
      - Press releases and political papers, 1988-1992 (Box 385, Folder 5)
      - Roundtables, 1987-1989 (Box 385, Folder 6)
    - National Institutes of Health, 1993 (Box 385, Folder 7)
    - National Lesbian and Gay Health Foundation, 1986, 1989 (Box 385, Folder 8)
    - National Minority AIDS Council, 1988-1990, 1993 (Box 385, Folder 9)
    - New York AIDS Coalition
      - AIDS Awareness Day, 1990 (Box 385, Folder 10)
      - Board of Directors
        - General, 1989-1990 (Box 385, Folder 11-12)
        - Meetings, 1990-1992 (Box 385, Folder 13)
        - Retreat, 1990 (Box 385, Folder 14)
      - Committee for AIDS Funding, 1990 (Box 385, Folder 15)
      - Funding, 1989-1990, 1993 (Box 386, Folder 1)
      - Meetings, 1990 (Box 386, Folder 2)
      - Statements of purpose, 1988, 1992 (Box 386, Folder 3)
    - New York AIDS Consortium, 1989-1990 (Box 386, Folder 4)
    - New York City AIDS Fund, 1988-1990 (Box 386, Folder 5)
    - New York City AIDS Task Force
      - Agenda and minutes, 1988-1990 (Box 386, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 386, Folder 7)
      - Creation of NYCATF, 1988 (Box 386, Folder 8)
      - Data Workgroup, 1988 (Box 386, Folder 9)
      - Funding issues, 1988 (Box 386, Folder 10)
      - Models of Care Workgroup, 1988 (Box 387, Folder 1-2)
      - Needs Assessment Workgroup, 1988 (Box 387, Folder 3)
      - Various policy statements, 1987-1990 (Box 387, Folder 4)
    - New York City Board of Education, 1986-1987, 1992 (Box 387, Folder 5-6)
    - New York City Coalition for Family Planning, 1988 (Box 387, Folder 7)
    - New York City Commission on Human Rights, 1989-1993 (Box 387, Folder 8)
    - New York City Department of Health, 1990 (Box 387, Folder 9-10)
    - New York City Department of Mental Health, 1990-1991 (Box 387, Folder 11)
    - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation, 1989-1991 (Box 387, Folder 12-13)
    - New York City Human Resources Administration, 1988-1990 (Box 387, Folder 14)
    - New York City Tuberculosis Workgroup, 1992-1993 (Box 387, Folder 15)
    - New York Community Trust, 1990 (Box 387, Folder 16)
    - New York Education File, 1990 (Box 388, Folder 1)
    - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers, 1987-1989 (Box 388, Folder 2)
    - New York State AIDS Institute
      - General, 1989-1992 (Box 388, Folder 3-5)
      - Correspondence, 1986, 1989-1990 (Box 388, Folder 6)